frankfinn.com 2019-07-02

# - Air Hostess Training Centre

Frankfinn Aviation Services Pvt. Ltd., a company incorporated under the Companies Act 1956, including its subsidiary companies, divisions and units, partners and associates (hereinafter together as “Frankfinn”) is committed to protecting your privacy online. Frankfinn has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy.

The following document outlines our corporate policies and practices with respect to Information gathering, dissemination and protection. By using this Website, you agree to the terms of the Frankfinn Privacy Policy outlined below.

 **What information do we collect?**  
Frankfinn does not collect any information about you other than the information that you affirmatively choose to submit to us.

 **How do we use your information?**  
The information submitted by you to us shall be used only by Frankfinn, its subsidiary companies, divisions and units, partners and associates to make better business decisions towards our mutual advantage, support the activities you choose to engage in, and provide higher quality solutions and services to you. We do not sell, share, or rent this information, for commercial purposes, to any person or organization.

Unless you have informed us that you do not wish to receive further information about our services/products and those of our affiliates and partners, we and they may contact you through phone or send you direct email. You may withdraw your consent at any time to use the information submitted by you by writing an email to us in this regard.

National Do Not Call Registry Regulation Frankfinn will not be responsible for any NDNC (National Do Not Call) Registry regulation that comes into play. You hereby agree and give your express assent to Frankfinn that even if you are registered under NDNC, DND (Do Not Disturb), Frankfinn will have the valid authority and your unconditional consent to call you regarding Frankfinn’s products and services till the time you expressly revoke your consent in writing.

 **Use of Cookies**

Cookies are small files which many web sites transfer to your hard disk.  
They can inform the web site what pages you visit, and your preferences, which enable web sites to provide you with a more personalized service. You can set your browser to refuse cookies, or to warn you before accepting them.

 **Links to other websites**

Our website might contain links to websites of third parties. If you link to their sites, they may collect information, and such sites are not within our control and are not covered by this privacy statement.

If we believe that your use of the site is unlawful or damaging to others, we reserve the right to disclose the information we have obtained through the site about you to the extent that it is reasonably necessary in our opinion to prevent, remedy or take action in relation to such conduct.

 **Change in the Privacy Policy**

Frankfinn reserves the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at its own discretion without any notice to you. We advise you to visit this page regularly to be aware of the latest version of our Privacy Policy.
